maniacstore.com 2015-06-01

# Privacy Policy | Maniacstore.com

We valued your trust in Maniacstore.com. That's the reason we insist upon the high standards for secure transactions and customer Identification information Privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about our privacy policy.

**Note:** Our privacy policy is subject to change without any prior notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review our privacy policy periodically.

###  **Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**

We collect personal identification information such as email address, your name, contact number, etc. from you when you create a free account with Maniacstore.com. While you can browse some sections of our website without being a registered member, certain activities including place an order do require registration.

We will use your contact information to send you new offers based on your previous orders and your interests at maniacstore.

###  **Demographic Information and Profile Data**

We use your personal information to provide you the services which you request to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, help promote a safe service, measure your interest in our products and services, inform you about latest offers about products or services, customize your experience, detect and protect against error, protect against fraud and other criminal activity, enforce our terms and conditions and described to you at the time of collection.

We identify your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you profile and demographic information.

We will ask you to complete optional online surveys which may ask you for contact information with demographic information such as zip code, age, or income level.

###  **Cookies**

A "cookie" means small information stored by a Web server on a Web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember specific information to a given user. We place permanent and temporary cookies in your computer's hard drive. Our cookies don’t contain any of your personal information.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

###  **Sharing of personal information**

We will share your personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates. Those entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in.

We will disclose your personal information if it’s required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process.

We will share all of your personal information with another business entity. Should such a transaction occur that other business entity will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information.

###  **Links to other Websites**

Our site links to other websites that may collect your personally identification information. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

###  **Choice/Opt-Out**

We provide all users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential or promotional communications from us on behalf of our partners.  
If you want to remove your contact information from Maniacstore.com lists and newsletters, than please contact us at [info@maniacstore.com](mailto:info@maniacstore.com).

###  **Advertisements on Maniacstore.com**

We will use third-party advertising companies for serve ads when you visit maniacstore website. Advertising companies will use information (not including your name, your address and email address, or contact number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about products and services of interest to you.

We have a tie-up with [www.cuponation.in](http://www.cuponation.in/) for coupons and deals along with out other affiliates as well.

###  **Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [info@maniacstore.com](mailto:info@maniacstore.com)

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to

**Maniac Store**  
**Office no. - 01, Ground Level,**  
**President House, Opp C. N. Vidyalay,**  
**Ambawadi, Ahmedabad - 380006,Gujarat (India)**

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

###  **Questions**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

**Maniac Store**  
**Office no. - 01, Ground Level,**  
**President House, Opp C. N. Vidyalay,**  
**Ambawadi, Ahmedabad - 380006,Gujarat (India)**
